ILGWU Photographs 5780 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Photographs
1835-1992
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5780 P
73.14 cubic feet
68.1 linear ft.
Photographs.
The ILGWU Photograph collection consists of photos of agreements, conventions, meetings, union members. Also included are photos of famous union leaders, such as; Antonini Luigi, Leon Stein, Abe Beame, Leon Blum, Sol Chaikin, Wilbur Daniels, max Danish, John Dewey, David Dubinsky, Israel Feinberg, Samuel Gompers, Arthur Goldberg, William Green among many other officials and members.
7461808
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 20, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, June 26, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780 PNGP: ILGWU Glass Plate Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N35: ILGWU 35mm Negatives of Photographs 5780 P N45: ILGWU 4x5 Negatives of Photographs
Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- Photographs; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- Photographs; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union--Photographs
7461808
- Aging, Conference on (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  includes: group photos and conference - David Dubinsky, Hon. Nelson Rockefeller; circa 1970
- Agreements [folder 1 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 2)
  includes: Signing between Montreal Joint Board Dress Makers Union & Montreal Manufacturers Guild - 8/6/56 - B. Shane, J.J. Spector; Local 91; Boston BAG Agreement; Local 20 - 12/15/50; Agreement between Associated Corset and Brassiere Manufacturers & Locals 10 & 32; Julius Hochman, David Dubinsky, Luigi Antonini; Dressmakers Agreement at NYC City Hall
- Agreements [folder 2 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agreements [folder 3 of 3] (Box 1, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Labor - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  includes: William Green and David Dubinsky holding 1940 affiliation certificate, with Hochman and Antonini; Adlai Stevenson and David Dubinsky at Convention of 1952, Matthew Woll, William Green, James Petrillo, President Dwight D. Eisenhower; David Dubinsky and George Meany; David Dubinsky and William Green; David Dubinsky, George Meany and FDR Jr.; Samuel Gompers with W.P. Mooty (1922); Samuel Gompers - Portrait; AFL Leaders with President Harry S. Truman and Senator Paul Douglas; David Dubinsky and Jacob Potofsky; AFL-CIO Meeting including John L. Lewis, Sidney Hillman, Phil Murray, Dan Tobin, Thomas Pinkert, Matthew Woll, and Harry Bates - 3/10/39
- American Federation of Labor - selected [folder 2 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 6)
- American Federation of Labor [folder 1 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 7)
  includes: Convention Photos; David Dubinsky and William Green; Meany, Goldberg, David Dubinsky; Luigi Antonini, David Dubinsky; David Dubinsky, Meany, Cherne, Vanden Heuvel; David Dubinsky and Jacob Potofsky - 1958; Shop scene with women promoting ILGWU; David Dubinsky and William Green holding ILGWU Certificate of Affiliation; Meany, David Dubinsky, Antonini; Banquet scene: Harry Van Arsdale, Zimmerman, David Dubinsky; President Dwight D. Eisenhower, David Dubinsky; Schnitzer, David Dubinsky; Dolores Johnson and David Dubinsky at Convention; Minoru Takita & George Meany - 11/10/64; Yorti & David Dubinsky; AFL-CIO Building Dedication; David Dubinsky, President Dwight D. Eisenhower; Group Shots; AFL-CIO Convention - David Dubinsky, President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Luigi Antonini - September 1951; Antonini, David Dubinsky; Bar - Yaacov, Evron, Boneh, David Dubinsky, Curran, Lavon, Potofsky, Geijer, Carey at AFL-CIO Convention; Harrison, Lavon, Potofsky, Meany, David Dubinsky at AFL-CIO Luncheon; Schnitzer & Dubinsky on Submarine Cruise; Eisenhower & David Dubinsky; Laying of a floral wreath at a Chicago Memorial
- American Federation of Labor [folder 2 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Labor [folder 3 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 9)
- American Federation of Labor [folder 4 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 10)
- American Federation of Labor [folder 5 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 11)
- American Federation of Labor [folder 6 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 12)
- American Federation of Labor [folder 7 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 13)
- American Federation of Labor [folder 8 of 8] (Box 1, Folder 14)
- American Labor Party - selected (Box 1, Folder 15)
  includes: Meany, David Dubinsky, Henry A Wallace at banquet and convention
- American Labor Party (Box 1, Folder 16)
  includes: Political Convention - David Dubinsky, Nagler, Zimmerman, LaGuardia, T. Dewey, L. Antonini
- American Veterans Committee (Box 1, Folder 17)
  includes: Banquet Shots America's Next Great Designer Award - includes: Award Ceremony - Wilbur Daniels, Kasper, Ernest Harris, Chaikin, Janet Riley; includes ceremony transcript
- Antonini, Luigi - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 19)
  includes: Luigi Antonini - Portrait, Demonstration with Placards for "Extra Pay for Overtime;" Antonini at Local 22 Rally; Julius Hochman, George Meany, David Dubinsky, L. Antonini at meeting
- Antonini, Luigi - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Antonini, Luigi (see also: Bx. 49 ff 1) [folder 1 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 21)
  includes: L. Antonini - Portrait; L. Antonini, David Dubinsky at banquet; Antonini and George Baldanzi visited the Fifth Army, September 1944; Italian American Labor Council Luncheon: Count Carlo Sforza, Herbert Matthews, L. Antonini; Governor Lehman and L. Antonini at Conference; Antonini in Shop Scene; Group Photo*; Edward Molisani, William Green, Hon. Thomas Dewey, Generoso Pope; Antonini and Golda Meir; Portrait of Antonini in Military Uniform; Antonini speaking to Local 89; Antonini marching with ILGWU Contingent in Columbus Day Parade, Nagler, Arthur Goldberg; Zimmerman, Stulberg, L. Antonini; Bernard Segal; Josephine Carboneri; Antonini and Contardo
- Antonini, Luigi (see also: Bx. 49 ff 1) [folder 2 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Antonini, Luigi (see also: Bx. 49 ff 1) [folder 3 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Antonini, Luigi (see also: Bx. 49 ff 1) [folder 4 of 4] (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Antonini, Luigi [folder 1 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 1)
  includes: Antonini and David Dubinsky meeting, dedication of Luigi Antonini Ave. in New York City; Antonini speaking; Antonini - Portrait; Local 89 Installation meeting including: David Dubinsky, Kramer, Antonini, Salvatore Noto; Antonini and Montana in Mondello, Italy at the Franklin Delano Roosevelt Institute; Joint Committee of the United Italian American Labor Council and the Order of the Sons of Italy at White House Meeting - Antonini, President Lyndon B. Johnson, J. Ottaviani Jr., Baldanzi, Molisani, Noto, Culotta, La Capria, Montana; Group photos; Banquet photos; Antonini Stadium in Haifa, Israel
- Antonini, Luigi [folder 2 of 2] (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Arbitration - Selected (Box 2, Folder 2a)
- Arbitration (Box 2, Folder 3)
  includes: arbitration meetings; Abe Plotline "speaking to officer qualification class on methods of organization"; Cloak Arbitration; Dress Industry Conference - arbitration for wage increase, 4/28/53, Hotel Astor, New York City; L. Antonini signing an agreement in the presence of Mayor Wagner
- Baltimore (Box 2, Folder 4)
  includes: David Dubinsky, Murray Gross at a conference; Ralph Smith "addressing strike meeting at Appomattox, Virginia"; David Dubinsky speaking at banquet, Upper South, 1954; David Dubinsky in a group shot with women. Bambace, Angela - see: Upper South Department
- Baruch (Box 2, Folder 5)
  includes: David Dubinsky and Baruch meeting
- Beame, Abe - selected (Box 2, Folder 5a)
- Beame, Abe (Box 2, Folder 6)
  includes: Abe Beame in shop scene; Beame in Political campaign
- Blum, Leon - selected (Box 2, Folder 7)
  includes: Leon Blum speaking; Blum meeting with David Dubinsky
- Blum, Leon (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Leon Blum Memorial Meeting, Manhattan Center, 4/6/50, including: A. Kahn, L. Weiner, W. Austin, David Dubinsky, J. Potofsky, H. Morganthau, M. Woll, N. Thomas, A. Cahan, R. Abramovitch, A. Held; At banquet, David Dubinsky, Blum; Blum speaking
- Blum, Leon - Album [folder 1 of 4] (Box 2, Folder 8a)
- Blum, Leon - Album [folder 2 of 4] (Box 2, Folder 8b)
- Blum, Leon - Album [folder 3 of 4] (Box 2, Folder 8c)
- Blum, Leon - Album [folder 4 of 4] (Box 2, Folder 8d)
- Boston - selected (Box 2, Folder 8e)
- Boston [folder 1 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Includes: "Trade Union Joan of Arcs" marching in January, 1936; Group Photo - Chorus, 2/20/51; Boston Joint Board - Soldiers returning from war; Picket of Vanta Co.; Group Photo - Children; "Keep em in Stitches", 1947 at Boston Joint Board; Children's Plays; Banquets; Choir performing; Stage performance with flags and clothing of ethnic groups and countries; AFL Convention, C. Kreindler, W. Green; H.T. Johnson Strike and picketing, 5/1/58; Harvard Centennial, June 1946, "When Bosses began dropping weights out of windows, Boston pickets donned helmets"; Mary Levin in group photo where members are holding checks in the air; District Council Meeting, Hotel Bradford, April 1948; Gay Nineties Revue, ILG Chorus; National ILGWU Convention; John McCormack, Philip Kramer, and Edward Milano at dedication of Radiology Department in memory of Harriet McCormack, at Boston Health Center; M. Klien, M. Kaplan, P. Kramer, N. Sandler, A. Polcari at Philip Kramer's retirement luncheon at Local 73; Blauer Manufacturing Company strike and picketing, September 1970; Anti-Smoking Demonstration; Benjamin Wensky, M. Kaplan, P. Kramer at a party for Boston Joint Board Cloakmakers (Wensky was 100 years old, charter member and former exec. board member of Local 56), May 1969; Political banquet for Humphrey/Muskie, October 1968; Fitwell Dress Co., Inc. Picket; Judy Bond Inc. strike with picketing; ILG Union Label Campaign with Sol Chaikin, Louis Stulberg, David Gingold, and Min Matheson; Joe Kessler and Rose Pesotta, Kramer Dinner, 6/4/60 (ff 18); Rally by ILGWU Retirees to "Stop Importing Unemployment."
- Boston [folder 2 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Boston [folder 3 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Boston [folder 4 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Boston [folder 5 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston [folder 6 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Boston [folder 7 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Boston [folder 8 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Boston [folder 9 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Boston [folder 10 of 10] (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Brandeis, Justice Louis (Box 2, Folder 19)
  includes: Portrait
- Brandt (Box 2, Folder 20)
  includes: Brandt, Clay, David Dubinsky at a meeting. Brown, Ella Clark - includes: Retirement Banquet for Morris Speitzer, Walter Reuther, Ella Clark Brown, Edward Arnold
- Buildings - selected (Box 2, Folder 21)
  includes: Fouard Building & Hester St. Park; ILGWU Headquarters, 1710 Broadway, New York City; Cooper Union, New York City
- Buildings [folder 1 of 5] (Box 2, Folder 22)
  includes: ILGWU Building; Clinton Hall; ILGWU Union Health Center, Fall River, Mass; ILGWU Health Center, Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania; ILGWU Health Center, Boston, Mass; ILGWU Health Center, San Antonio, Texas; Eastern District Office; ILGWU Health Center, 257 7th Ave, New York City; Manhattan Lyceum; Kaiser - Frazer; ILGWU Educational Center, South Jersey; Los Angeles Cloak Joint Board; Los Angeles Health Center; Tri-District, Wilkes-Barre; Ackerman Clothes; Harlem Office, Joint Board Dressmakers Union; Pacific Coast Office; Mobile Health Center, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania; Cleveland Health Center; St. Louis Health Center; Philadelphia Health Center; Local 48, New York City; Plans for the Home for the Aged, Grace Ave., New York; Knit Goods Workers Local 190,. Philadelphia; Kansas City Health Center; St Louis Joint Board; ILGWU Library
- Buildings [folder 2 of 5] (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Buildings [folder 3 of 5] (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Buildings [folder 4 of 5] (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Buildings [folder 5 of 5] (Box 2, Folder 26)
- ILGWU Convention at World's Fair, New York, June 2, 1940, Black and white photograph (Box 2OP, Folder 1)
- 40th Anniversary, I.L.G.W.U., New York City, May 27-June 8, 1940, Black and white photograph (Box 2OP, Folder 2)
- Italian Dressmakers Union, Local 89, June 16, 1973, Black and white photograph (Box 2OP, Folder 3)
- Banquet, 25th Convention, I.L.G.W.U., Hotel Statler, Boston, Mass., June 3, 1944, Black and white photograph (Box 2OP, Folder 4)
- Cahan, Abe - selected (Box 3, Folder 1)
  includes: Cahan - contact sheet
- California - selected (Box 3, Folder 2)
  includes: David Dubinsky and Rose Pesotta at train station, Nathan Wolf, Louis Levy; Blouse Workers Strike; Union Rally. See also: 5780/46 - Box 3 - 4
- California (Box 3, Folder 3)
  includes: Nathan Wolf, Rose Pesotta; David Dubinsky, Rose Pesotta, Louis Levy, Nathan Wolf at train station; banquet scene; Rose Pesotta; David Dubinsky and Louis Stulberg honored at meeting of the Los Angeles Local of the ILGWU; David Dubinsky - Banquet scene; Jimmy Walker and Rose Pesotta; In a meeting/ conference: Ian West, Lou Tabak, Mitchel, David Dubinsky
- Canada, Montreal - selected (Box 3, Folder 4)
  includes: Rose Dress Strike - Picket Line; French and English broadside; Police arresting a picketer in 1937; First Cloak Agreement - Secretary of the Joint Council Mrs. Shuster, Max Kaiser, Albert Eaton, J. Bonchik, D. Goodman, I. Wolkore, B. Shane, Emile Lazare; Montreal Organization Campaign 1954; Demonstration with placards in Montreal's Garment District, 1977
- Canada, Montreal [folder 1 of 8] (Box 3, Folder 5)
  includes: Carl Goldenberg, William Green, Bernard Shane, David Dubinsky, Percy Bengough, J.J. Spector; Delegation Meeting David Dubinsky at the Railway Station, 1940; David Dubinsky, Bernard Shane - Montreal, August 23, 1950; Bernard Shane, William Green; Magali & Claude Jauniere, Denise Martineau; Raoul Trepanier, Maurice Manel, Sam Lieberman, Bernard Shane, Claude Jodoin & W. Perkel; Julius Hochman, H.S. Greenwood, Claude Jodoin, Bernard Shane; Dave Goodman, Annette Langevin, J.J. Spector, David Dubinsky, Irving Brown, Joe Godson, Morris Novick, Serafino Romunoldi; Bernard Shane, Hon. Antonio Banette, David Dubinsky, Hon. Gaspard Fairteux; Bernard Shane, General Morton, Hon. Antonio Banette, Carl Goldenberg, H.H. Stein, Claude Jodoin; Harry Capitani, Gordon Cushing; ILGWU Chorus; Bernard Shane with new & old Queens; Shop Scene - Women and Men Pressers; Dressmakers Weekend Institute - Oct. 19-21, 1956, Hotel Vermont, Quebec - Maurice Manel, Bernard Shane, J.B. Lafrwniere, Yvette Charpentier, J.L. Blanchard; Bernard Shane & George Meany; April 19, 1956 - Check Presentations by Bernard Shane to Histadrut & the Jewish Labour Committee; Montreal Health Center Tour; M. Mitchell, G. Robinson, Lloyd Lenton, Henry Weisbach; J. Mack, S. Herbst, B. Shane, Sam Kraisman; Joint Council Cloakmakers Union Meeting; Exec. Board, Local 315 - Al Meakins, Dora Boudreault, Nathan Rosen, Yvonne Bourque, Bernard Shane, Valerine Chabot, Rolandi Briesbois, Adriano Bussandri, Morris Amsel, J.J. Spector, Louis Manzi, Victor Souliere, Marcel D'Amour; Presentation of a cheques from the ILGWU to the strikers at the plant of the Regent Knitting Mills in St. Jerome; David Dubinsky, Bernard Shane; Atul Chandra Saikia, Bernard Shane; Alexandria, Ontario ILGWU Headquarters; B. Tabachinsky, Michael Rubenstein, Bernard Shane; Signing Contract between Montreal Joint Board Dressmakers Union & the Montreal Dress Manufacturers' Guild, 8/6/1956; ILGWU Convention; Executive Board Meeting, Local 205; Canadian Labor Congress Demonstration, Ottawa; Claude Jodoin; Bresner, Stulberg, Jraisman, Jodoin, Manel, Magerman, Shatz; Chateau Lingerie Mfg. Co. Ltd. Strike; Demonstration for limiting clothing imports, Advertisements for Union Label on clothing; Silver Fashion Inc. picket, Labor Day Demonstration, Early 1930's; Mayor Chameleon Houde addressing strikers meeting to approve settlement in 1940; Building Dedication - David Dubinsky; Canadian Coordination Conference, 7/31/69
- Canada, Montreal [folder 2 of 8] (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Canada, Montreal [folder 3 of 8] (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Canada, Montreal [folder 4 of 8] (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Canada, Montreal [folder 5 of 8] (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Canada, Montreal [folder 6 of 8] (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Canada, Montreal [folder 7 of 8] (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Canada, Montreal [folder 8 of 8] (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Canada, Toronto - selected (Box 3, Folder 13)
  includes: Group photo of: Joint Board Cloak, Shirt, Dressmakers Union, Toronto 1917-1918 - Kirsner, Edwards, Kruger, Black, Shure, Koldofsky, Yanpolsky, Konikoff, Seligman, Wilner, Sporn, Kosatchkoff, Wilner, Friedman, Surber, Samuels, Anin, Franklyn, Fox, Weintraub, Sheinkman
- Canada, Toronto (Box 3, Folder 14)
  includes: Bernard Shane presenting A. Abramson with a check at a meeting; "Child Workers who Need 'Protocol' Arbitration Courts", the Independent Gertrude Barnum, 10/3/12
- Chaikin, Sol Chick, 1960s (Box 3, Folder 15)
  selected (see also: Bx. 49 ff 2) - includes: Banquet scene; outside a banquet David Rosalind, Ted Kennedy, Chaikin; Chaikin speaking at ILGWU Convention, May 1968, Speech at Rhode Island AFL-CIO
- Chaikin, Sol Chick, 1960s [folder 1 of 5] (Box 3, Folder 16)
  includes: Esther Peterson and Louis Stulberg speaking to Rhode Island AFL-CIO; Banquet scenes; Meetings; Frank Lavigne, J. William Belanger, Jack Halpern, Chaikin, Foster Furcolo, Thomas Moriarty; Ted Kennedy; Chaikin, Herman Greenburg, P. Boland, Anna Sullivan; David Dubinsky speaking at a banquet; Chaikin at Albano Testimonial; Chaikin at Convention, Scranton, PA; individual shot of Chaikin
- Chaikin, Sol Chick, 1960s [folder 2 of 5] (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Chaikin, Sol Chick, 1960s [folder 3 of 5] (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Chaikin, Sol Chick, 1960s [folder 4 of 5] (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Chaikin, Sol Chick, 1960s [folder 5 of 5] (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Chicago (Box 3, Folder 21)
  includes: Bernard Bialis at a banquet; Rachael Hermandy, Max Wax, David Dubinsky, Morris Bialis, Chicago Joint Board Representatives, Employers' Representatives 5/16/1953; Group Shot at meeting - Jerry Adelman, Harry Rufer, Morris Bialis, Maurice Smoler, Sam Glassman, Stanley Johnson, Sidney Smoler, Sol Greenburg; Chicago Joint Board Baseball Team, 1936
- China (Box 3, Folder 22)
  includes: children at the washboard; landscape photos, children working in a factory (not a garment factory)
- City of Hope and Sanatoriums - selected (Box 3, Folder 23)
  includes: David Dubinsky and Exec. Board at Deborah Sanitorium
- City of Hope and Sanatoriums (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Dedication of a Jewish Sanitorium, David Dubinsky, 1/7/1951; David Dubinsky, Luz Romero, Sally Balducci, Maria Rosales, Herda Gluckner, Hyman Langer; John Sargent of the Hotel, Restaurant and Bartenders International Union presenting a check, 7/15/1949; George Meany, David Dubinsky. William Green at Banquet honoring Meany at the Waldorf Astoria Hotel in New York City, 5/7/1952
- Civil Rights - selected (Box 4, Folder 1)
  includes: Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. speech; Dr. King presented with a Social Justice Award; Local 62 - Demonstration with placards by Black Women against Woolworth, "Woolworth practices Discrimination in the South. Don't Patronize"; Shop Scene where Black and White women stop working on April 9, 1968 to listen to funeral services for Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr.: Group Photo next to a bus with a sign "Prayer Pilgrimage I.L.G.W.U."; Local 142 Discussion Group Trade Unionism, 2/4/1935, black & white men & women listening to Black man speak; Ottenheimer Employees on strike with placards; Dr. M. L. King giving a speech
- Civil Rights [folder 1 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 2)
  includes: Civil Rights Demonstration with placards in front of the White House, Washington DC; David Dubinsky, Harry Van Arsdale, Martin Luther King in press conference and Contact Sheet; Ottenheimer Employees on Strike with placards - fighting "Unfair Labor Practices" and "Years of Bad Treatment"; Civil Rights Committee on minimum wages with Abe Dolyen and Congressman Jim Delaney; Banquet scene - on dais - David Dubinsky and Martin Luther King; King and David Dubinsky meeting; Kansas City Joint Board Little League Baseball Team; Local 91 Mandolin Orchestra, Sept. 1934; VP Charles Zimmerman, meeting with CORE National Director James Farmer, CORE Community Relations Director Marvin Rich, and ILA Organizational Director Anthony Scotto; Civil Rights Rally - 7th Ave and 38th Street, New York City, 5/17/1960; Picket in front of Ottenheimer Mfg. Co., against Unfair Labor Practices; Local 22 Basketball Team; ILGWU Workers from Locals 105, 89, 35, 60, and 23 demonstrating with placards to "End Segregation"; Press Conference with African Trade Unionists at ILGWU Training Institute - Louis Stulberg, Olakunle Thomas, Joyce Chanda, Charles Pasipanodya, Anselmi Karumba, Guy Boghossian, Maida Springer Kemp and Gus Tyler
- Civil rights [folder 2 of 2] (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated - selected (Box 4, Folder 4)
  includes: Group Shot in front of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; David Dubinsky and Potofsky speaking
- Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  includes: J.P. Stevens Workers demonstrating with placards "Boycott J.P. Stevens Products," "#1 Labor Law Violator" in Scranton, PA - Led by VP Sol Hoffman and Jack Sobol; Demonstration with Placards - "CWA Supports ACTWU in their Fight Against Imports" and "We want Work, Not Welfare"; David Dubinsky, Potofsky at a Gathering; Picket against J.P. Stevens - Local 23-25; Rally against J.P. Stevens - Shelley Appleton and Wilbur Daniels in front of the firm's headquarters in New York City, November 30, 1978; At a banquet: David Dubinsky, Potofsky
- Cohn, Fannia - selected (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Cohn, Fannia (see also: 5780/49 Bx. 11 ff 8-11) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  includes: Group photo of Local 145 members
- Columbus, Christopher (Box 4, Folder 8)
  includes: Antonini, Governor Lehman, David Dubinsky, S. Gelo, and E. Jewish, Columbus Day at 89 Opera at Hippodrome
- Committee for Industrial Organization (CIO) - selected (Box 4, Folder 9)
  includes: CIO Meeting in Pittsburgh, November 7 & 8, 1936; Julius Hochman, David Dubinsky, Sidney Hillman, John L. Lewis, Philip Murray at Meeting; Matthew Woll talking with press